{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424625965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424625964"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424626928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424626928"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424629856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424629856"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424630390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424630390"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424631032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424631032"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424635188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424635187"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424636111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424636111"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424639729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424639729"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424640515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424640515"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424641490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424641490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424645383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424645383"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424646347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424646347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424649262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424649261"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424649805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424649804"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424650449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424650449"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424654581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424654581"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424655515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424655513"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424659172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424659172"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424659967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424659966"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424660952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424660951"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424663467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424663467"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424663533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424663533"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" a4dfadfc-378b-4de6-9347-616d1048055c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424699867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424699867"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" 874dae19-85ca-4282-92c4-9f6cadab2144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima_mlima-mjomba-mbaya-ardhi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mlima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424723652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424723652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" 874dae19-85ca-4282-92c4-9f6cadab2144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi_kimya-kuna-kasi-tofauti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" tofauti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424726601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424726600"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" 874dae19-85ca-4282-92c4-9f6cadab2144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi_kimya-kuna-kasi-tofauti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424729712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424729712"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" 874dae19-85ca-4282-92c4-9f6cadab2144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi_kimya-kuna-kasi-tofauti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" kimya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424736028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424736028"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" 874dae19-85ca-4282-92c4-9f6cadab2144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi_kimya-kuna-kasi-tofauti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" kasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424762610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424762609"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" 874dae19-85ca-4282-92c4-9f6cadab2144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara_barabara-kuna-au-gani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" barabara"," userResponse":" barabara"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424765123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424765122"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" 874dae19-85ca-4282-92c4-9f6cadab2144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" barabara_barabara-kuna-au-gani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424765189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424765189"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" 874dae19-85ca-4282-92c4-9f6cadab2144"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424773307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424773306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424773538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424773538"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424774513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424774512"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424775800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424775799"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424778718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424778717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424779574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424779574"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424779896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424779895"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424781141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424781140"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424784731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424784730"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424785726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424785725"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424785980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424785979"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424786924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424786924"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424789794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424789793"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424790842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424790842"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424791324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424791323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424795887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424795884"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548424795963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548424795963"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_165648"," gameId":" f57ed53e-cc24-49ab-ad52-440771aab26d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}